Broadcast Center Recordings, circa 1980-2017: Finding Aid AC362
University Archives
- Series 7: Broadcast Center Recordings, 2014-2016; 760 items
  - Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership Third Annual Meeting - Biotechnology for the Sustainable Production of Fuels and Chemicals, 2014 November 14; ENE-Corporate Affiliates; 2 items (Item 3059D)
    Speakers: Jose L. Avalos; "Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership hosts an annual meeting that brings together E-ffiliates members, other industry representatives, policy leaders, and members of the Princeton University community; run time: 32:06
  - Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership Third Annual Meeting - Panel Discussion Investing in Energy and Sustainability, 2014 November 14; 2 items (Item 3060D)
    Speakers: Caroline Dorsa, Carter F. Bales, Emily A. Carter, Andrew K. Golden, Richard L. Kauffman; "Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership hosts an annual meeting that brings together E-ffiliates members, other industry representatives, policy leaders, and members of the Princeton University community; run time: 1:34:49
  - Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership Third Annual Meeting - Panel Discussion Large Format Energy Storage, 2014 November 14; ENE-Corporate Affiliates; 2 items (Item 3061D)
    Speakers: Daniel A. Steingart, Paul Albertus, Glenn G. Amatucci, Corie Cobb, Alexander Couzis; "Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership hosts an annual meeting that brings together E-ffiliates members, other industry representatives, policy leaders, and members of the Princeton University community; run time: 1:26:58
  - Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership Third Annual Meeting - Controlling Microcracking in Low Embodied Energy Concrete, 2014 November 14; ENE-Corporate Affiliates; 2 items (Item 3062D)
    Speakers: Claire E. White; "Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership hosts an annual meeting that brings together E-ffiliates members, other industry representatives, policy leaders, and members of the Princeton University community; run time: 32:59
  - Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership Third Annual Meeting _Fifth Assesment Report of the Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change, 2014 November 14; ENE-Corporate Affiliates; 2 items (Item 3063D)
    Speakers: Michael Oppenheimer; "Princeton E-ffiliates Partnership hosts an annual meeting that brings together E-ffiliates members, other industry representatives, policy leaders, and members of the Princeton University community; run time: 47:36
  - ISC 231/ISC 232, 2014 November 14; LSI-Chair; 2 items (Item 3246D)
    Speakers: run time: 51:14
  - Steven B. Smith lecture, 2014 November 14; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3247D)
    Speakers: Steven B. Smith; "Steven B. Smith, Alfred Cowles Professor of Government and Philosophy, Yale University gives a lecture on Lincoln's Enlightenment.; run time: 1:35:25
  - Political Dissent, Digital Media, and Futures of Academic Freedom, 2014 November 17; HIS-Collaborative History; 2 items (Item 3248D)
    Speakers: Max Weiss, Stephen Salaita; run time: 1:23:31
  - Architecture Achim Menges and Jenny Sabin, 2014 November 19; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3064D)
    Speakers: Achim Menges, Jenny Sabin; run time: 2:31:28
  - PADAWAN (Princeton Application Developer And Web Admin Network) Meeting, 2014 November 21; OIT-Acad Tech Svcs; 2 items (Item 3065D)
    Speakers: Michael Muzzie; run time: 1:23:42
  - Title IX panel investigations training, 2014 November 24; VCL-Programming; 2 items (Item 3066D)
    Speakers: All Princeton University administrators: Cheri Burgess, Michele Minter, Sankar Suryanarayan, Victoria Jueds, etc; "Training session will start with individual speakers at the front of the room, followed by role plays (involving five participants) and large-group discussion with the audience; run time: 1:46:20
  - PACM Distinguished Lecture Series, 2014 December 4; APC-Applied and Comp Math; 2 items (Item 3249D)
    Speakers: Jennifer Chayes; "Annual PACM Distinguished Lecture. Jennifer's talk is titled \"Belief Propagation Algorithms: From Matching Problems to Network Discovery in Cancer Genomics\"; run time: 1:03:56
  - Andlinger Center for Energy and the Environment Highlight Seminar Series Joan Brennecke, 2015 January 16; Princeton University. Andlinger Center For Energy And Environment; 2 items (Item 3134D)
    Speakers: Joan Brennecke; "Andlinger Center for Energy and the Environment Highlight Seminar Series; run time: 59:38
  - The Triumph and Tragedy of Israel, 2015 January 20; ORL-Jewish Life; 2 items (Item 3135D)
    Speakers: Ari Shavit, moderated by Ambassador Daniel Kurtzer; run time: 1:17:11
  - HIS304 Modern Latin America Since 1810, 2015 February 2; HIS-Undergraduate; 2 items (Item 3136D)
    Speakers: Rob Karl; run time: 46:46
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 2; 2 items (Item 3175D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 34:29
  - Judge Janice Rogers Brown Lecture, 2015 February 3; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3250D)
    Speakers: Judge Janice Rogers Brown; "Judge Janice Rogers Brown, U. S. Court of Appeals for the D.C. Circuit. Herbert W. VAugusthan Lecture on America's Founding Principles; run time: 1:36:07
  - Architecture Spring 15 Lecture Series - Lynn, Hoberman and Rockwell, 2015 February 4; 2 items (Item 3067D)
    Speakers: Greg Lynn, Chuck Hoberman, David Rockwell; "\u201cMotion Dynamics\u201d with Greg Lynn, Founder and Principal, Greg Lynn Form; Chuck Hoberman, Founder and President of Hoberman Associates Inc.; and David Rockwell, Founder and President of the Rockwell Group; run time: 2:02:00
  - HIS304 Modern Latin America Since 1810, 2015 February 4; HIS-Undergraduate; 2 items (Item 3137D)
    Speakers: Rob Karl; run time: 52:23
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 4; 2 items (Item 3176D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 44:34
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 9; 2 items (Item 3177D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 46:15
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 11; 2 items (Item 3178D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 45:47
  - The Christians of Syria and Lebanon and Their Arab Spring, 2015 February 12; Princeton university. Department of Near Eastern Studies; 2 items (Item 3138D)
    Speakers: Jack Tanous, Mary Mikhael; "Lecture in the series \"The Near East and the World Seminar Series: Christianity and the Near East: Past, Present\u2026 Future?\"; run time: 53:17
  - 2014/2015 ACEE Highlight Seminar Series - Kartik Chandran, 2015 February 16; Princeton University. Andlinger Center For Energy And Environment; 2 items (Item 3179D)
    Speakers: Kartik Chandran; run time: 1:13:13
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 16; 2 items (Item 3180D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 47:54
  - Princeton Rutgers Consortium, 2015 February 17; PNI-Princeton Neuro Institute; 2 items (Item 3139D)
    Speakers: Sam Wang, Manny DiCicco-Bloom; "The Princeton Neuroscience Institute and Rutgers Brain Health Institute are pleased to announce a new seminar series for postdocs and PhD students in neuroscience and related fields; run time: 1:54:33
  - Malcolm X: Life After Death, 2015 February 17; ORL-Islamic Life; 2 items (Item 3251D)
    Speakers: Dr. Eddie Glaude, Dr. Sohail Daulatzai, Ali Newman, Kameelah Rashad, Imam Zaid Shakir; run time: 2:31:59
  - Architecture Spring 2015 Lecture Series - Winka Dubbeldam, 2015 February 18; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3068D)
    Speakers: Winka Dubbeldam; run time: 1:15:37
  - Schwarzman Scholarship Information Session, 2015 February 18; 2 items (Item 3181D)
    Speakers: Deirdre Moloney, Robert Garris, Stephen Scwarzman; run time: 1:13:33
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 18; 2 items (Item 3182D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 46:17
  - Princeton on Language - Casey Lew Williams, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3069D)
    Speakers: Casey Lew Williams; " Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields.; run time: 9:21
  - Princeton on Language - Sarah-Jane_Leslie, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3070D)
    Speakers: Sarah_Jane Leslie; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields.\n\n; run time: 9:20
  - Princeton on Language - Bernard Haykel, 2015 February 20; 2 items (Item 3071D)
    Speakers: Bernard Haykel; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 10:13
  - Princeton on Language - Rosina Lozano, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3072D)
    Speakers: Rosina Lozano; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 8:01
  - Princeton on Language - Michael Gordin, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3073D)
    Speakers: Michael Gordin; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 7:31
  - Princeton on Language - Brian Kernighan, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3074D)
    Speakers: Brian Kernighan; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 7:58
  - Princeton on Language - Christina Lazaridi, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3075D)
    Speakers: Christina Lazaridi; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 8:11
  - Princeton on Language - Simon Morrison, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3076D)
    Speakers: Simon Morrison; "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 8:40
  - Princeton on Language - Drummer, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3077D)
    Speakers: "Immerse yourself in the world of language in this performance-like educational session that will bring together members of the faculty and students\u2014representing a range of disciplines and interests\u2014to reflect on the concept of language in their fields; run time: 3:49
  - A Conversation on Women and the Eating CLubs, 2015 February 20; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3183D)
    Speakers: Lisa Schmucki \u201974, Joanna Anyanwu \u201915, Julyia Blount \u201912, Joe Margolies \u201915, Lucia Perasso \u201916, Jennifer Zhao \u201915; " An important and timely conversation for all members of the Princeton community, this event will bring together alumni and student panelists to discuss the current eating club culture as it relates to female members; run time: 1:31:41
  - 2015 Alumni Service of Remembrance, 2015 February 21; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3252D)
    Speakers: run time: 1:12:34
  - Alumni Day 100th Anniversary Promo, 2015 February 21; VPS-Other Programs; 2 items (Item 3279D)
    Speakers: run time: 4:42
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 23; 2 items (Item 3184D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 44:07
  - The 12th Annual Edward W. Said Memorial Lecture: The State of Palestine, 2015 February 23; Princeton university, Department of English; 2 items (Item 3185D)
    Speakers: Tariq Ali; run time: 1:19:34
    Princeton university, Department of English
    The English Department of Princeton University was founded by University President Woodrow Wilson in 1904. Although courses in English and American literature had been offered at Princeton since as early as 1864, the Department flourished after Wilson's appointment of seven distinguished Preceptors of English in 1905. Since that time, Princeton has remained one of the top English faculties in the nation, recognized especially for its combined emphases on scholarship and teaching. Through the twentieth century the Department has been noted for its contributions to philology, literary history, American Studies, literary theory, and most recently, feminist scholarship and theory. Graduate study has been a major component of the Department's life since the foundation of the Graduate School (1901), and English has always remained one of the University's most popular undergraduate concentrations.
  - Panel on Moderation and Conservatism, 2015 February 24; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3253D)
    Speakers: Sam Tanenhaus, Peter Berkowitz, Aurelian Craiutu; run time: 1:30:19
  - Architecture Spring 15 Lecture Series - Bernard Tschumi, 2015 February 25; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3078D)
    Speakers: Bernard Tschumi; run time: 1:42:59
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 February 25; 2 items (Item 3186D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 47:43
  - The Modern Aramaic dialects of the Christians and Jews of Iraq and Iran, 2015 February 26; Princeton university. Department of Near Eastern Studies; 2 items (Item 3140D)
    Speakers: Geoffrey Khan; "Near East and World Seminar Series; run time: 1:14:45
  - Thomas Siebel - New Business Ideation, 2015 February 26; DOC-Office of Dean of College; 2 items (Item 3254D)
    Speakers: Thomas Siebel; run time: 1:11:58
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 March 2; 2 items (Item 3187D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 44:27
  - Admissions Congratulations Video, 2015 March 3; WWS-Graduate-Admissions; 2 items (Item 3255D)
    Speakers: run time: 2:47
  - Tanner Lectures on Human Values, 2015 March 4; Princeton University. University Center for Human Values; 2 items (Item 3079D)
    Speakers: Elizabeth Anderson, David Bromwich, Ann Hughes; run time: 1:56:38
  - Architecture Spring 15 Lecture Series - Hashim Sarkis, 2015 March 4; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3141D)
    Speakers: Hashim Sarkis; run time: 1:28:11
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 March 4; 2 items (Item 3188D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 46:27
  - Producing Waste / Producing Space, 2015 March 7; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3284D)
    Speakers: run time: N/A
  - 2014/2015 ACEE Highlight Seminar Series - Grey, 2015 March 9; Princeton University. Andlinger Center For Energy And Environment; 2 items (Item 3189D)
    Speakers: Grey; run time: 1:13:48
  - Admiral Michael Rogers Talk, 2015 March 10; USV-CES-Representative 2; 2 items (Item 3256D)
    Speakers: Dean Vince Poor, Don Dixon '69, Admiral Michael Rogers, Ed Felton; run time: 57:15
  - Admiral Michael Rogers Q and A, 2015 March 10; USV-CES-Representative 2; 2 items (Item 3257D)
    Speakers: Dean Vince Poor, Don Dixon '69, Admiral Michael Rogers, Ed Felton; run time: 57:44
  - Abre los ojos: un puente!, 2015 March 13; SPO-Spanish & Portugese; 2 items (Item 3080D)
    Speakers: Ignacio Paya-Laforteza; "Visiting Professor for Distinguished Teaching of Civil and Environmental Engineering and the Keller Center for Innovation in Engineering Education; run time: 49:02
  - Golda Meir: American Roots, Zionist Life, 2015 March 23; HUM-American Studies; 2 items (Item 3081D)
    Speakers: Hendrik Hartog, Pnina Lahav; "Annual Lapidus Lecture in American Jewish Studies; run time: 1:12:19
  - Steve Mills '81 Sports, Race and Society Lecture, 2015 March 24; Princeton University. Center for African American Studies; 2 items (Item 3258D)
    Speakers: Adam Silver, Steve Mills '81, Craig Robinson '83, Eddie S. Glaude Jr.; "American athletes, and black athletes in particular, have a storied history of showing political awareness on, and off, the field and court\n\n; run time: 58:48
  - Architecture Spring 2015 Lecture Series - Jonathan Massey, 2015 March 25; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3142D)
    Speakers: Jonathan Massey; run time: null
  - Where Do We Go From Here?, 2015 March 25; Princeton university, Department of English; 2 items (Item 3190D)
    Speakers: Jamie Broadax, Elizabeth Minkel, Anne Jamison, Heidi Tandy, Emily Nussbaum; "What happens when a much-mocked \"fringe\" culture spawns a generation of writers? How can commercial interests interact with a global, not-for-profit community whose members are marginalized, diverse, and often fearful of discovery; run time: 1:48:05
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 March 25; 2 items (Item 3191D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 48:34
  - The Mediators: Christians in the Service of Islamic Culture, 2015 March 26; Princeton university. Department of Near Eastern Studies; 2 items (Item 3259D)
    Speakers: Peter Starr; "Near East and World Seminar Series; run time: 58:32
  - \"Fluvial Metropolis\" March workshop Morning Session, 2015 March 27; Princeton Environmental Institute; 2 items (Item 3143D)
    Speakers: run time: 2:36:25
  - \"Fluvial Metropolis\" March workshop Afternoon Session, 2015 March 27; Princeton Environmental Institute; 2 items (Item 3144D)
    Speakers: run time: 2:33:01
  - Lightning in a Panel: The American Superhero and the Invention of a Modern Mythology, 2015 March 27; DOC-WRI-Writing Program; 2 items (Item 3192D)
    Speakers: Paul Levitz, Dennis O'Neil, Louise Simonson, Walter Simonson, Larry Hama; Sajan Saini; "university-wide event, inviting five veteran comics writers to speak on the origins of superhero narratives in comics and the recent proliferation of this genre into other major media; run time: 1:33:00
  - The Intimacies of Four Continents, 2015 March 30; HUM-American Studies; 2 items (Item 3082D)
    Speakers: Lisa Lowe; "Public Lecture on Asian American Studies; run time: 1:25:54
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 March 30; 2 items (Item 3193D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 41:38
  - HUM 218 Voltaire lecture, 2015 March 31; HUM-Council of the Humanities; 2 items (Item 3083D)
    Speakers: Anthony Grafton; "50 minute lecture for HUM 218-219. \n\n; run time: 53:00
  - PRISM/PCCM seminar series, 2015 April 1; PSM-Graduate; 2 items (Item 3145D)
    Speakers: Rod Priestley, Jay Benziger, Martin Bazant; run time: 1:04:31
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 April 1; 2 items (Item 3194D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 45:33
  - IHUM Program \"The Aesthetics of Mathematics\, 2015 April 2; HUM-IHUM; 2 items (Item 3084D)
    Speakers: Reviel Netz; run time: 1:15:06
  - Latin America in Construction Symposium Part 1, 2015 April 3; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3146D)
    Speakers: "Symposium in conjunction with the exhibition \"Latin American in Construction\"; run time: 2:07:59
  - Latin America in Construction Symposium Part 2, 2015 April 3; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3147D)
    Speakers: "Symposium in conjunction with the exhibition \"Latin American in Construction\"; run time: 1:59:09
  - Latin America in Construction Symposium Part 3, 2015 April 3; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3148D)
    Speakers: "Symposium in conjunction with the exhibition \"Latin American in Construction\"; run time: 1:55:50
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 April 6; 2 items (Item 3195D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 46:33
  - Guy Fi: THe Fictions that Shape Men's Lives - Chris Kilmartin, 2015 April 6; UHS-Health Prom and Prevent-SHARE; 2 items (Item 3260D)
    Speakers: Chris Kilmartin; run time: 1:28:40
  - Edge Lecture - Francis Fukuyama, 2015 April 7; DOF-Public Lectures; 2 items (Item 3085D)
    Speakers: Francis Fukuyama; "Francis Fukuyama, Political Scientist and author of \"The End of History\" will deliver the Edge Lecture; run time: 1:13:48
  - David Lisak training sessions Part 2, 2015 April 7; UHS-Health Prom and Prevent-SHARE; 2 items (Item 3149D)
    Speakers: "David Lisak, Regan Crotty; run time: 1:28:42
  - Lisak Training Session with Appellate Bodies, 2015 April 8; UHS-Health Prom and Prevent-SHARE; 2 items (Item 3086D)
    Speakers: David Lisak; run time: 1:20:17
  - Wilson Signature Lecture presents Peter Sellars, 2015 April 8; DOC-Wilson College; 2 items (Item 3087D)
    Speakers: Peter Sellars, American Theater Director; run time: 1:40:18
  - Sociology From E Street: Bruce Springsteen's America, 2015 April 8; 2 items (Item 3196D)
    Speakers: Mitch Duneier; run time: 47:29
  - Gilbert Meilaender Lecture, 2015 April 9; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3088D)
    Speakers: Gilbert Meilaender, Senior Research Professor, Valparaiso University Charles E. Test, MD; run time: 1:32:21
  - Smart Data Pricing Forum - Dennis Strigl, 2015 April 9; Princeton University. Department of Electrical Engineering; 2 items (Item 3197D)
    Speakers: Dennis Strigl; run time: 57:20
  - Smart Data Pricing Forum - How to Charge, 2015 April 9; Princeton University. Department of Electrical Engineering; 2 items (Item 3198D)
    Speakers: run time: 1:34:23
  - Smart Data Pricing Forum - Open Toll-Free and Zero-Rating Panel, 2015 April 9; Princeton University. Department of Electrical Engineering; 2 items (Item 3199D)
    Speakers: run time: 1:31:39
  - City Lost and Found Symposium, 2015 April 9; Princeton university. School of architecture; 2 items (Item 3291D)
    Speakers: run time: Multiple Video Files
  - Gilbert Meilaender Conference - Session 1, 2015 April 10; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3089D)
    Speakers: "Politics, Theology, and the Limits of Ethics A Conference Celebrating the Work of Gilbert Meilaender; run time: 1:38:28
  - Gilbert Meilaender Conference - Session 2, 2015 April 10; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3090D)
    Speakers: run time: 1:38:12
  - Gilbert Meilaender Conference - Session 3, 2015 April 10; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3091D)
    Speakers: "Politics, Theology, and the Limits of Ethics A Conference Celebrating the Work of Gilbert Meilaender; run time: 1:45:20
  - Gilbert Meilaender Conference - Session 4, 2015 April 10; James Madison Program in American Ideals and Institutions; 2 items (Item 3092D)
    Speakers: "Politics, Theology, and the Limits of Ethics A Conference Celebrating the Work of Gilbert Meilaender; run time: 38:36